Hello everybody and welcome to EnglishPod.
大家好，欢迎收听EnglishPod。
My name is Marco.
我是Marco。
My name is Catherine and we hope by now you're very excited about football or soccer.
我是Catherine，希望到现在你们对足球或英式足球已经非常兴奋了。
This is the World Cup time of year so this comes every four years actually and we've
现在是一年一度的世界杯时间，实际上每四年一次，我们
got a lesson all about it.
准备了一堂关于它的课程。
That's right.
没错。
So as everyone may or may not have heard, we are actually in the middle of the World
所以，不管大家有没有听说，我们现在正处在世界杯期间，
Cup and as you say it's a football or soccer competition.
正如你所说，这是一场足球或英式足球比赛。
Now soccer is only used in the United States.
不过“soccer”这个词只在美国使用。
That's right.
没错。
It's used in the United States although football can be confusing in a place like Australia
在美国确实这么用，但在澳大利亚这样的地方，“football”可能会让人困惑，
where they have two different games that are called football.
因为他们有两种不同的比赛都叫“football”。
That's right.
没错。
So it's a little bit difficult at times to tell someone that you play football and they
所以有时候很难跟别人说清楚你踢的是哪种足球，他们
think you play American football or Australian football or soccer.
可能会以为你玩的是美式橄榄球、澳式足球或者英式足球。
So it's a little bit confusing.
所以有点让人困惑。
It can be, yeah.
确实会这样。
All right.
好了。
So we have a great lesson all about the World Cup.
所以我们有一堂很棒的世界杯课程。
We're going to explain a little bit and so let's listen to the dialogue for the very
我们会稍微解释一下，现在让我们第一次
first time.
听对话。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
What am I doing?
我在干什么？
Don't you know what day it is?
你不知道今天是什么日子吗？
Um, no.
嗯，不知道。
It's only the day when the world's biggest sporting event is kicking off.
今天是世界上最大的体育赛事开幕的日子啊。
What?
什么？
The World Cup.
世界杯啊。
The first match is today.
第一场比赛就在今天。
It's Mexico versus South Africa.
是墨西哥对南非。
It's going to be a really good match.
这会是一场非常精彩的比赛。
Both teams have a very strong offense and have skilled players.
两支球队都有很强的进攻能力和技术娴熟的球员。
I think that South Africa will probably dominate the first half since they are the host country
我觉得南非可能会在上半场占优势，因为他们是东道主
and all.
之类的。
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我完全不知道你在说什么。
The only sporting event we watch at home is the Super Bowl.
我们在家看的唯一体育赛事就是超级碗。
This is bigger than the Super Bowl, man.
这比超级碗还大啊，老兄。
Teams from 32 countries compete against each other every four years and fight to win that
来自32个国家的球队每四年互相竞争，争夺那个
trophy.
奖杯。
They first start in a group stage with eight groups, each group having four teams.
他们先从小组赛开始，有八个小组，每组四支球队。
The top two teams pass on to an elimination stage before going on to the semifinals and
前两名球队进入淘汰赛阶段，然后进入半决赛和
the quarterfinals.
四分之一决赛。
Sounds interesting, but soccer doesn't really appeal to me.
听起来挺有意思，但足球真的吸引不了我。
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吗？
Over 700 million people watched the final match of the 2006 World Cup.
超过7亿人观看了2006年世界杯的决赛。
It's a very exciting and nerve-wracking sport.
这是一项非常激动人心又让人紧张的运动。
Each nation is cheering on their team, hoping they will become the next champion.
每个国家都在为自己的球队加油，希望他们能成为下一个冠军。
So far, Brazil is the team with the most titles under their belt.
到目前为止，巴西是获得冠军次数最多的球队。
They're really good.
他们真的很厉害。
All I know about soccer is that you can't use your hands and that players are always
我对足球的了解就是不能用手，而且球员总是
falling down trying to get a free kick or penalty kick.
摔倒，想骗个任意球或点球。
It seems like a sissy sport to me.
在我看来这像是一项娘娘腔的运动。
Whatever.
随便吧。
I'm going to go watch the opening match.
我要去看开幕赛了。
All right, we're back.
好了，我们回来了。
So obviously, two people discussing or fighting over the World Cup and soccer.
很明显，两个人在讨论或者说争论世界杯和足球。
One of them doesn't really like it.
其中一个人不太喜欢它。
But he came up with some really interesting points and explained a couple of interesting
但他提出了一些很有趣的观点，也解释了一些有趣的
things.
事情。
So let's take a look at some of that vocab on Language Takeaway.
所以让我们在“语言小贴士”环节看看一些词汇。
Language Takeaway.
语言小贴士。
So, okay, the very first phrase here is a very important one.
好的，这里的第一个短语非常重要。
We're talking about sports.
我们在谈论体育。
This game is called a sporting event.
这种比赛叫做体育赛事。
That's right.
没错。
So a sporting event is an event, I guess you would say is a performance or something that
所以体育赛事就是一个事件，我想你可以说是一场表演或偶尔
happens occasionally, but related to sports.
发生的事情，但与体育相关。
That's right.
没错。
So an event can be a game itself or a tournament.
所以一个事件可以是一场比赛本身，也可以是一个锦标赛。
You've heard maybe of well, the UEFA Cup, that's the European Federation of Football
你可能听说过，比如欧洲联盟杯，那是欧洲足球联合会
or whatever it is.
之类的。
So basically, you have this tournament for European soccer teams.
基本上，这是为欧洲足球队举办的锦标赛。
But the World Cup is also an event and a very important game could also be an event.
但世界杯也是一个赛事，一场非常重要的比赛也可以算作一个事件。
So this basically means a sporting match or a sporting competition.
所以这基本上就是指一场体育比赛或体育竞赛。
That's right.
没错。
Now it may sound confusing as to why you put the ing in sport.
现在可能听起来有点困惑，为什么要在“sport”后面加“ing”。
It should be maybe sports event or sport event, but I'm not really sure why we add the gerund
按理说应该是“sports event”或“sport event”，但我不太确定为什么我们要加动名词
to sporting event.
变成“sporting event”。
We always just say it this way.
我们一直就这么说。
It's a set phrase.
这是一个固定短语。
So let's remember that it's sporting event.
所以我们要记住，这是体育赛事。
This is the world's most important sporting event, for example.
例如，这是世界上最重要的体育赛事。
Okay, very good.
好的，非常好。
Now we went and we talked about the first match, Mexico versus South Africa, and they're
现在我们继续，聊到了第一场比赛，墨西哥对阵南非，他们
talking about the teams and how they both have a very strong offense.
在讨论两支球队，以及它们都有非常强的进攻能力。
Okay, so offense is a part of the team.
好的，所以“进攻”是球队的一部分。
Basically it's a group of players who are trying to score.
基本上，它是一组试图得分的球员。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, so when you're good at offense, it means you're good at scoring.
好的，所以如果你擅长进攻，就意味着你擅长得分。
And the opposite of offense is what?
那么“进攻”的反义词是什么？
Defense.
防守。
So offense, defense.
所以，进攻、防守。
You can say they have a very strong defense.
你可以说他们防守非常强。
That means that it's very hard to score against them because their defenders, their goalies,
这意味着很难在他们身上得分，因为他们的后卫、守门员
they're all very strong.
都非常强大。
That's right.
没错。
So we're talking about an offense and a defense, both very important parts of a team.
所以我们讨论的是进攻和防守，都是球队非常重要的部分。
And so the guy continued and made a little bit of a prediction saying that South Africa
然后那个人继续说，并做了一点预测，说南非
will probably dominate the first half.
可能会主导上半场。
Okay, so you know that football matches are split into halves.
好的，你知道足球比赛是分成半场的。
You have first half and second half.
有上半场和下半场。
To dominate here means to be stronger than someone else.
这里“主导”的意思是比对手更强。
So to control the ball or to have possession or to be the one that is the strongest team
所以就是控制球权、掌握控球，或者成为场上最强的队伍，
on the field.
在球场上。
That's right.
没错。
So you can dominate by having a very strong defense or you can dominate by having a very
所以你可以通过强大的防守来主导，也可以通过强大的
strong offense or both.
进攻来主导，或者两者兼备。
Dominate means be stronger than.
“主导”就是比对手更强。
That's right.
没错。
Okay, now let's move on to the other guy who doesn't really like soccer.
好的，现在我们来说说另一个不太喜欢足球的家伙。
And he says, I have no idea what you're talking about.
他说，我完全不知道你在说什么。
All I know is that I watch the Super Bowl.
我只知道我看超级碗。
Okay, now this is a very American thing, the Super Bowl.
好的，超级碗是一个非常美国化的东西。
That's right.
没错。
We mentioned earlier that in America, most people call the game soccer, not football.
我们之前提到过，在美国，大多数人把这项运动叫做“soccer”，而不是“football”。
Well, that's because in America, we have a different game called football.
嗯，那是因为在美国，我们有另一种不同的运动叫“football”。
That's right.
没错。
And so the Super Bowl is like the most important game in the football world.
而超级碗就像是橄榄球界最重要的比赛。
It's the game that happens every year at the very end of the season.
这是每个赛季末都会举行的比赛。
That's right.
没错。
So this is what we usually call American football.
这就是我们通常所说的美式橄榄球。
So you've probably seen it on TV as well.
你可能也在电视上看过。
And the Super Bowl is basically the name of the final sporting event of American football.
超级碗基本上就是美式橄榄球最后一场赛事的名称。
Just like we have World Cup, we have the Super Bowl.
就像我们有世界杯一样，我们也有超级碗。
And the winner of the Super Bowl is the best team that year.
超级碗的冠军就是当年最强的球队。
That's right.
没错。
All right, so now let's go on to explain a little bit about how the World Cup works.
好了，现在我们来解释一下世界杯的运作方式。
The guy went on to explain that there are 32 countries competing.
那个人接着解释说有32个国家参赛。
And basically, we have three parts, an elimination stage, a semifinals, and quarterfinals.
基本上，我们分为三个阶段：淘汰赛、半决赛和四分之一决赛。
Okay, so basically, this describes the different levels because obviously, 32 teams can't compete
好的，这基本上描述了不同的阶段，因为显然，32支球队不能一开始就
for one trophy at first.
争夺一个奖杯。
You have to make the numbers smaller.
你得把队伍数量减少。
So 32 becomes 16, becomes 8, becomes 4, becomes 2.
所以32支变成16支，变成8支，变成4支，变成2支。
That's right.
没错。
And so we have different groups for these.
所以我们有不同的小组来对应这些阶段。
The first one is the elimination stage when some teams lose and they go home.
第一个是淘汰赛阶段，有些球队输了就回家了。
That's right.
没错。
And after that, then we have a quarterfinals.
之后，就是四分之一决赛。
So what is quarterfinals?
那么什么是四分之一决赛？
The quarterfinals are when you have eight teams that are basically the top eight teams
四分之一决赛就是有八支队伍，基本上是比赛中的前八名
of the competition.
的参赛队伍。
And they will play against one other opponent.
他们会与另一个对手进行比赛。
So the winner passes on to the next stage, which would be the semifinals.
所以胜者进入下一阶段，也就是半决赛。
Well, the math makes sense because quarter has to do with four, right?
嗯，数学上说得通，因为“quarter”和四有关，对吧？
So in the quarterfinals, eight teams become four.
所以在四分之一决赛中，八支队伍变成四支。
And in the semifinals, four teams become two.
而在半决赛中，四支队伍变成两支。
That's right.
没错。
And then what happens after the semifinals?
那半决赛之后会发生什么？
And then we have the final, where basically the two top teams will compete against each
然后就是决赛，基本上两支顶尖队伍会相互竞争
other and there will be one champion.
最终产生一个冠军。
USA!
美国队！
And this is when it gets very nationalistic.
这时候就变得非常民族主义了。
People are very proud of their countries.
人们为自己的国家感到非常自豪。
Of course, of course.
当然，当然。
And so this basically is what happens and how we get our champion.
所以这基本上就是比赛的过程，以及我们如何产生冠军。
And well, now let's explain a little bit very quickly about two things that happen in the
好了，现在我们快速解释一下比赛中发生的两件事，
game during gameplay when we have a free kick and a penalty kick.
就是任意球和点球。
Okay, so a kick, you know, you just kick the ball.
好，所以踢球，你知道，就是踢球。
But sometimes when the ball goes out of bounds or when a player is injured or there's a foul,
但有时候当球出界，或者球员受伤，或者有犯规时，
then that player or his teammate can take a special kick.
那么那个球员或他的队友可以踢一个特殊球。
All right.
好的。
And so a free kick is, it's just a kick from anywhere, right?
所以任意球就是，从任何地方踢的球，对吧？
A free kick is a kick that you get basically according to the referee who says, okay, stop
任意球基本上是根据裁判的判罚，他说，好，停止
the game.
比赛。
He's going to kick from inside the lines.
他会在边线内踢球。
That's right.
没错。
So wherever you are fouled, wherever somebody maybe hit you wrong or something happened
所以无论你在哪里被犯规，无论有人可能撞到你或发生什么事，
from that position, you will kick freely towards the goal or wherever you want.
从那个位置，你可以自由地向球门或任何地方踢球。
You can pass to your other players as well.
你也可以传给其他队友。
That's right.
没错。
But a penalty kick is a bit different because you have to be in a special place when you
但点球有点不同，因为你必须在特殊位置
do it.
踢。
That's right.
没错。
A penalty kick is when you are fouled inside the box, what they call it, in the area very
点球是指你在禁区内被犯规，他们称之为，在非常靠近
close to the goalie.
守门员的区域。
So if you commit a foul there, then the other player will receive a penalty kick and it
所以如果你在那里犯规，那么对方球员会得到一个点球，
will just be him against the goalie and he must kick the ball.
就只是他对阵守门员，他必须踢球。
I think it's approximately 10 meters if I'm not mistaken.
我想如果我没记错的话，大约是10米。
Yes.
是的。
And this is why it's very dangerous because you're so close to the goalie and no one can
这就是为什么它非常危险，因为你离守门员这么近，没人能
stop you.
阻止你。
And so when fouls happen inside that special box, it's usually bad news for the goalie.
所以当犯规发生在那个特殊区域内时，对守门员来说通常是坏消息。
Yeah, of course.
是的，当然。
So this is what happens during a penalty kick and well, basically you have no defenders.
所以这就是点球时发生的情况，基本上你没有防守队员。
So it's just you, the goalie, and it can get, as you said, very complicated for the goalie.
所以只有你、守门员，而且就像你说的，对守门员来说可能变得非常复杂。
So all right, so we've taken a look at a lot of things on Language Takeaway.
好了，我们在“语言要点”部分看了很多东西。
Let's move on now to three phrases on Fluency Builder.
现在让我们继续看“流利度构建”部分的三个短语。
Fluency Builder.
流利度构建。
Okay, so this is a great word to describe how I felt last week when I watched the England
好的，这是一个很好的词，用来描述我上周看英格兰
versus America match.
对美国比赛时的感受。
I thought it was a nerve-wracking game.
我觉得那是一场令人紧张的比赛。
That's right.
没错。
Okay.
好的。
And we heard this in the dialogue, right?
我们在对话中听到了这个，对吧？
Yeah, you said it was a very nerve-wracking game or in the dialogue the guy said, it's
是的，你说这是一场非常令人紧张的比赛，或者在对话中那个人说，这是
a very exciting and nerve-wracking sport.
一项非常刺激且令人紧张的运动。
So if something's nerve-wracking, what does it mean?
所以如果某件事令人紧张，它是什么意思？
Well basically if you break it down, nerves are those things in your body, in your skin
基本上，如果你分解这个词，神经是你身体里、皮肤里的那些东西，
that make you feel.
让你有感觉。
So if someone hurts you, you feel it because of your nerves.
所以如果有人伤害你，你会感觉到，因为你的神经。
So something that is nerve-wracking makes you nervous.
所以令人紧张的事情会让你紧张。
It makes you anxious.
它让你焦虑。
It makes you feel very sensitive.
它让你感觉非常敏感。
That's right.
没错。
So of course the sporting event is so exciting and you're worried that your country or your
所以当然体育赛事非常刺激，你担心你的国家或你的
team will lose that you're very nervous and you're very excited, you're very anxious.
球队会输，所以你非常紧张，非常兴奋，非常焦虑。
A lot of things are going on.
很多事情在发生。
Maybe you're sweating, maybe you're drinking a lot.
也许你在出汗，也许你在喝很多酒。
You don't want to know.
你不想知道。
You don't want to see your team lose and so you get very nervous.
你不想看到你的球队输，所以你会变得非常紧张。
That's right.
没错。
And now of course if your team is in the World Cup, you are cheering on for your team or
现在当然如果你的球队在世界杯中，你会为你的球队加油，
you're cheering them on.
或者你为他们加油。
Okay, so this is an interesting phrase because maybe you've heard the word to cheer before,
好的，这是一个有趣的短语，因为也许你以前听过“cheer”这个词，
you know, go team, go team.
你知道，加油，加油。
This is cheering.
这就是加油。
But we often say I want to cheer him on.
但我们经常说我想为他加油。
So this on to me means like I want to cheer him on to victory.
所以这个“on”对我来说意味着我想为他加油走向胜利。
I want to push them towards some goal.
我想推动他们朝着某个目标前进。
And so you hear this a lot.
所以你经常听到这个。
Let's cheer them on or he was really cheering me on.
让我们为他们加油，或者他当时真的在为我加油。
It made me feel good.
这让我感觉很好。
Motivating you.
激励你。
So to cheer someone on, cheer them on.
所以为某人加油，为他们加油。
All right.
好的。
So obviously this is why we have cheerleaders, right?
所以显然这就是为什么我们有啦啦队，对吧？
Girls that cheer.
加油的女孩们。
Give me an A. Give me a B.
给我一个A。给我一个B。
These are the girls or the group of girls that cheer teams on.
这些是为球队加油的女孩或女孩团体。
Or men too.
或者也有男性。
I've seen male cheerleaders.
我见过男性啦啦队员。
That's true.
没错。
All right.
好的。
And now when we talked about Brazil, they are the team with the most titles under their
现在当我们谈到巴西时，他们是拥有最多冠军头衔的球队，
belt.
在他们的腰带下。
Okay, we're not talking about a real belt here, are we?
好的，我们这里不是在说真正的腰带，对吧？
No.
不。
Under your belt or under their belt in this case means that in their history, they have
这里的“under your belt”或“under their belt”指的是，在他们的历史中，他们拥有
the most titles.
最多的冠军头衔。
That's right.
没错。
I think it may come from boxing or one of those sports where you actually wear a belt
我想这可能来自拳击或类似运动，在这些运动中你会佩戴一条腰带，
that says your title.
上面写着你的头衔。
And I think, if I'm not mistaken, sometimes a boxing belt will have various titles on
而且，如果我没记错的话，有时拳击腰带上会刻有各种头衔。
the belt.
对。
Right.
冠军腰带。
The championship belts.
是的。
Yeah.
因为他们之后会佩戴它。
Because they wear it afterwards.
我以前没听说过，但这确实有道理。
I've never heard that before, but it does make sense.
但这里要记住的重点是，这不只限于体育。
But the important thing to remember here is that it's not just sports.
你可以说，他在市场营销方面有10年的经验。
You could say he has 10 years of experience in marketing under his belt.
没错。
That's right.
所以这意味着他在市场营销方面很有经验。
So that means he's experienced at marketing.
没错。
That's right.
就是这样。
So that's right.
所以就是这样。
As you said, you can use it for work experience, you can use it for titles in work, or maybe
就像你说的，你可以用它来积累工作经验，也可以用它来获取工作头衔，或者
in education you can say he's got three master's degrees under his belt.
在教育领域，你可以说他已获得三个硕士学位。
Wow.
哇。
All right.
好吧。
So a lot of great stuff there.
所以这里有很多好东西。
We've taken a look at a lot of vocab, so I think we should listen to our dialogue again
我们已经看了很多词汇，所以我觉得我们应该再听一遍对话，
and we'll be back to talk a little bit more.
然后回来再聊一会儿。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
What am I doing?
我在干什么？
Don't you know what day it is?
你不知道今天是什么日子吗？
Um, no.
嗯，不知道。
It's only the day when the world's biggest sporting event is kicking off.
今天是世界上最大的体育赛事开幕的日子。
What?
什么？
The World Cup.
世界杯。
The first match is today.
第一场比赛就在今天。
It's Mexico versus South Africa.
是墨西哥对南非。
It's going to be a really good match.
这将是一场非常精彩的比赛。
Both teams have a very strong offense and have skilled players.
两支球队都有很强的进攻能力和技术娴熟的球员。
I think that South Africa will probably dominate the first half since they are the host country
我觉得南非可能会在上半场占据优势，因为他们是东道主国家。
and all.
等等。
I have no idea what you're talking about.
我完全不知道你在说什么。
The only sporting event we watch at home is the Super Bowl.
我们在家看的唯一体育赛事就是超级碗。
This is bigger than the Super Bowl, man.
老兄，这可比超级碗还盛大。
Teams from 32 countries compete against each other every four years and fight to win that
来自32个国家的球队每四年相互竞争，争夺那个
trophy.
奖杯。
They first start in a group stage with eight groups, each group having four teams.
他们首先从小组赛开始，有八个小组，每组四支球队。
The top two teams pass on to an elimination stage before going on to the semifinals and
每组前两名晋级淘汰赛，然后进入半决赛和
the quarterfinals.
四分之一决赛。
Sounds interesting, but soccer doesn't really appeal to me.
听起来挺有意思，但足球对我来说没什么吸引力。
Are you kidding?
你在开玩笑吧？
Over 700 million people watched the final match of the 2006 World Cup.
超过7亿人观看了2006年世界杯的决赛。
It's a very exciting and nerve-wracking sport.
这是一项非常刺激又让人紧张的运动。
Each nation is cheering on their team, hoping they will become the next champion.
每个国家都在为自己的球队加油，希望他们能成为下一个冠军。
So far, Brazil is the team with the most titles under their belt.
到目前为止，巴西是获得冠军头衔最多的球队。
They're really good.
他们真的很厉害。
All I know about soccer is that you can't use your hands and that players are always
我对足球的了解就是不能用手，而且球员们总是
falling down trying to get a free kick or penalty kick.
摔倒，试图获得任意球或点球。
It seems like a sissy sport to me.
在我看来，这像是一项娘娘腔的运动。
Whatever, I'm going to go watch the opening match.
随便吧，我要去看开幕式比赛了。
All right, so the World Cup, as we said, it gathers over 100 million people to watch the
好了，正如我们所说，世界杯在2006年吸引了超过一亿人观看决赛。
final in 2006.
决赛。
Now, this sport is not very popular in North America.
现在，这项运动在北美并不十分流行。
It's not totally true because Mexicans really follow football.
这不完全正确，因为墨西哥人真的很关注足球。
That's right.
没错。
But I think in America, in the United States, it is one of the less popular sports.
但我认为在美国，它是较不受欢迎的运动之一。
I was thinking the other day, maybe number five on our list of popular sports.
我前几天在想，它可能在我们最受欢迎的运动榜单上排第五。
Maybe because you have American football, the NFL, you have Major League Baseball, you
也许是因为你们有美式橄榄球（NFL）、美国职业棒球大联盟（MLB）、
have the NBA, you have the NHL, and I think maybe before soccer, you probably either have
NBA、NHL，而且我认为在足球之前，可能还有
golf or tennis before soccer, even though the United States does have its own Major
高尔夫或网球，尽管美国确实有自己的美国职业足球大联盟
League Soccer.
（MLS）。
Yep, MLS, Major League Soccer.
是的，MLS，美国职业足球大联盟。
And my hometown team is Chicago Fire, pretty good team.
我家乡的球队是芝加哥火焰队，相当不错的球队。
I heard they're very good.
我听说他们很厉害。
And the LA Galaxy, I think, is the other best team in the States.
而洛杉矶银河队，我认为是美国另一支最好的球队。
That's right.
没错。
Now, the United States did host the 1994 World Cup, and I think this is where a little bit
现在，美国确实主办了1994年世界杯，我认为这开始引发了
of more interest started to come up.
更多的兴趣。
And I think Major League Soccer was formed prior to the World Cup in the United States.
而且我认为美国职业足球大联盟是在世界杯之前成立的。
That's right.
没错。
Well, there's another part of it.
嗯，还有另一部分原因。
I mean, as young people, as children, we almost all played soccer.
我的意思是，作为年轻人，作为孩子，我们几乎都踢过足球。
I played soccer.
我踢过足球。
I know a lot of my friends did as well.
我知道我的很多朋友也踢过。
It's not popular everywhere, but a lot of people play it.
足球并不是到处都流行，但很多人都在踢。
And there's not really an audience for soccer in America once you're in the professional
在美国，一旦进入职业领域，足球其实没什么观众。
realm.
领域。
And so the problem is when you pass college, you don't think of it as the NBA, for example,
所以问题在于，大学毕业后，你不会把它当成NBA那样看待，比如，
because there's not as big of an audience.
因为观众没那么庞大。
And so people just end up doing their normal jobs as opposed to being professional soccer
于是人们最终就去做普通工作，而不是成为职业足球
players.
球员。
I think that has a big something to do with it is the fact that there is not as much money
我认为这很大程度上与这项运动在职业层面上的收入不如NBA有关，
in this sport professionally as, for example, the NBA.
比如。
Or prestige.
或者声望。
Exactly.
没错。
Although, this is the, on the other hand, these players that do make it and they really
不过，另一方面，那些真正成功并且非常想踢球的球员，
want to play, they go abroad and they go play in the European leagues or something like
他们会出国，去欧洲联赛之类的地方踢球。
that.
没错。
That's right.
And a lot of the players who were playing the other day against England were playing
而且前几天和英格兰比赛时，很多美国球员其实是在和他们的队友对抗，
against their teammates because so many of the American team, the American national team
因为美国队，也就是美国国家队里有很多人
play in the English Premier League.
都在英超踢球。
It was really awkward.
那场面挺尴尬的。
Well, it's a really great sport.
嗯，这确实是一项很棒的运动。
I think it's one of the most popular sports in many other countries as well because it's
我认为它在很多其他国家也是最受欢迎的运动之一，因为它
so easy.
很简单。
All you need is a ball.
你只需要一个球。
You need a group of people.
你需要一群人。
You put two rocks and you have a goal and you start playing.
放两块石头当球门，然后就能开始踢了。
And that's probably why it's the most international sport because it's very easy to set up.
这大概就是为什么它是最国际化的运动，因为很容易就能组织起来。
People all over the world love it and hopefully one day the United States will kind of push
全世界的人都喜欢它，希望有一天美国也能推动它，
it and...
然后……
Become champion.
成为冠军。
Yeah.
是啊。
Well, I hope this year they'll become champions but my fingers are definitely crossed because
嗯，我希望今年他们能成为冠军，但我肯定要祈祷一下，因为
who knows.
谁知道呢。
All right.
好了。
So, it's a really great topic.
所以，这是个很棒的话题。
We want to know if your country is in the World Cup.
我们想知道你的国家是否在世界杯中。
Have you ever qualified for a World Cup?
你们曾经晋级过世界杯吗？
There are still many countries who haven't made it.
还有很多国家从未晋级过。
Of course, it's a very small pool.
当然，名额非常有限。
Only 98, 199 countries compete to qualify for the World Cup and only 32 make it.
只有98个、199个国家竞争世界杯资格，最终只有32个能晋级。
And you can also tell us who you're supporting.
你也可以告诉我们你支持谁。
We won't judge.
我们不会评判的。
That's right.
没错。
So, we're waiting for your comments at EnglishPod.com.
所以，我们在EnglishPod.com等着你的评论。
We'll see everyone there.
我们会在那里见大家。
Bye.
再见。
All right, good luck.
好了，祝你好运。